A Guide to the Edgar B. Young papers FA109
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Lincoln Center, Inc., 1952-1980 (1956-1976); 1956-1976; 1; 26.48 Cubic Feet 68 letter document boxes, 1 legal document box, and 1 flat file folder; 69 Boxes 27.6 cubic feet
  - Art, 1960-1972; 2
    - Buildings - Philharmonic Hall - Works of Art (Acquisitions, etc.), 1962-1971 (1971) (Box 12, Folder 130)
    - Chermayeff and Lustig Contract, 1961-1965 (1973) (Box 12, Folder 131)
      See also RAC Photograph Collection, Series 1073, Box 1, Folder 3.
    - Albert A. List Foundation Gift for Art, 1961-1963 (1973) (Box 12, Folder 132)
    - Albert A. List Foundation Gift for Art, 1964-1971 (1973) (Box 12, Folder 133)
    - Miscellaneous Works of Art - Rejections and Incomplete Negotiations, 1960-1966 (1973) (Box 13, Folder 134)
    - Posters, 1961-September 13, 1963 (1973) (Box 13, Folder 135)
    - Posters, September 23, 1963-1969 (1973) (Box 13, Folder 136)
    - Sculpture - Calder, Alexander - Stabile "Guichet", 1964-April 11, 1965 (1973) (Box 13, Folder 137)
    - Sculpture - Calder, Alexander - Stabile "Guichet", April 15, 1965-1967 (1973) (Box 13, Folder 138)
    - 2 copies of floor plan for Calder sculpture, with letter., 1965 June; ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Quantity 2) (Drawer D 14, Folder 1)
      Separated from Series 1.2 Art, Box 13, Folder 138
    - Sculpture - Moore, Henry - "Reclining Figure", 1961-August 1964 (1973) (Box 13, Folder 139)
    - Sculpture - Moore, Henry - "Reclining Figure", September 1964-July 1965 (1973) (Box 13, Folder 140)
    - Sculpture - Moore, Henry - "Reclining Figure", August-September 1965 (1973) (Box 13, Folder 141)
    - Sculpture - Moore, Henry - "Reclining Figure", October-December 1965 (1973) (Box 13, Folder 142)
    - Sculpture - Moore, Henry - "Reclining Figure", 1966-1973 (1973) (Box 13, Folder 143)
    - Sculpture - Moore, Henry - "Reclining Figure", July 13, 1972 (1973) (Box 13, Folder 144)
    - Sculpture - Smith, David - "Zig IV", 1965-1969 (1973) (Box 13, Folder 145)
    - Sculpture - Smith, David - "Zig IV", 1965-1969 (1973) (Box 13, Folder 146)
    - Sculpture - James Wines Commission, 1965-1969 (1973) (Box 13, Folder 147)
  - Building Operations, 1958-1978; 3
    This subseries contains information about the costs, budgets, maintenance and operations of various buildings, including Avery Fisher Hall.
    - Maintenance and Budgets - Garage, 1963-1970 (Box 13, Folder 148)
    - Maintenance and Budgets - Garage, 1971-1972 (Box 13, Folder 149)
    - Maintenance and Budgets - General Services Committee, 1974-1975 (Box 13, Folder 150)
    - Maintenance and Budgets - General Services Committee, 1976-April 1977 (Box 14, Folder 151)
    - Maintenance and Budgets - General Services Committee, May-September 22, 1977 (Box 14, Folder 152)
    - Maintenance and Budgets - General Services Committee, September 27, 1977-May 1978 (Box 14, Folder 153)
    - Maintenance and Budgets - Juilliard Building - Costs and Budgets, 1963-August 12, 1964 (1971) (Box 14, Folder 154)
    - Maintenance and Budgets - Juilliard Building - Costs and Budgets, August 19, 1964-February 1966 (1971) (Box 14, Folder 155)
    - Maintenance and Budgets - Juilliard Building - Costs and Budgets, March-July 1966 (1971) (Box 14, Folder 156)
    - Maintenance and Budgets - Juilliard Building - Costs and Budgets, September 1966-March 1971 (1971) (Box 14, Folder 157)
    - Maintenance and Budgets - Juilliard Drama Division - Lincoln Center Fund - Summary Budgets, 1968-1969 (Box 14, Folder 158)
      Book 2 (No Book 1).
    - Maintenance and Budgets - Maintenance, Repairs and Operations, 1962-May 1964 (Box 14, Folder 159)
    - Maintenance and Budgets - Maintenance, Repairs and Operations, December 1964-March 1965 (Box 14, Folder 160)
    - Maintenance and Budgets - Maintenance, Repairs and Operations, April 1965-November 24, 1965 (Box 14, Folder 161)
    - Maintenance and Budgets - Maintenance, Repairs and Operations, November 29, 1965-1972 (Box 15, Folder 162)
    - Maintenance and Budgets - McKinsey & Company, Inc. - Management Consultants, 1964-1965 (Box 15, Folder 163)
    - Maintenance and Budgets - New York State Theater - General Files, 1961-1964 (1971) (Box 15, Folder 164)
    - Maintenance and Budgets - New York State Theater - Operations, 1958-1965 (1971) (Box 15, Folder 165)
    - Maintenance and Budgets - Operating Costs (Estimated), n.d., 1959-January 1960 (1971) (Box 15, Folder 166)
    - Maintenance and Budgets - Operating Costs (Estimated), February 1960-1962 (1971) (Box 15, Folder 167)
    - Correspondence and Floor plan for Opera Tower, Rockefeller Center., 1960 December; ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Quantity 1) (Drawer D 14, Folder 1)
      Separated from Series 1.3 Bldg. Ops., Box 15, Folder 167
    - Maintenance and Budgets - Philharmonic Hall - Complaints, 1963-1966 (1971) (Box 15, Folder 168)
    - Maintenance and Budgets - Philharmonic Hall - Income and Expenditures, 1966-1970 (1971) (Box 15, Folder 169)
    - Maintenance and Budgets - Philharmonic Hall - Operations, 1962-1963 (1971) (Box 15, Folder 170)
    - Maintenance and Budgets - Philharmonic Hall - Operations, 1964-1965 (1971) (Box 15, Folder 171)
    - Maintenance and Budgets - Philharmonic Hall - Report - "Strengthening the Operation of Lincoln Center" - McKinsey & Company, Inc., December 1964 (Box 15, Folder 172)
    - Maintenance and Budgets - Security - All Lincoln Center Buildings (Vincent Gillen Associates), 1964-1972 (Box 16, Folder 173)
    - Maintenance and Budgets - Special Committee on Rebuilding of Avery Fisher Hall, 1975-February 2, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 174)
    - Maintenance and Budgets - Special Committee on Rebuilding of Avery Fisher Hall, February 5-August 1976 (Box 16, Folder 175)
    - Maintenance and Budgets - Special Committee on Rebuilding of Avery Fisher Hall, September-October 1976 (Box 16, Folder 176)
    - Maintenance and Budgets - Subsidiary Corporations, 1962-1963 (1972) (Box 16, Folder 177)
    - Physical Plant, 1965-1966 (Box 16, Folder 178)
  - Constituent Relations, 1955-1978; 4
    Creating and maintaining a positive working relationship between Lincoln Center, Inc. and its constituents, as well as between each constituent, was essential to the success and growth of Lincoln Center. Each constituent negotiated its own contract with Lincoln Center, Inc. and subsequently abided by their individual agreements. Correspondence, negotiations and/or agreements are available with all the founding and major constituents as well as the early potential constituents including: The Philharmonic-Symphony Society, The Metropolitan Opera Association, Juilliard School, Library/Museum of the Performing Arts, the Repertory Theater of Lincoln Center, the Chamber Music Society, New York Shakespeare Festival, and the Film Society of Lincoln Center, Inc. Of special note are the agreements with Lincoln Center, Inc. of the Metropolitan Opera Association and the Philharmonic-Symphony Society as well as documentation of the special subcommittee on the Philharmonic musicians strike and the subsequent revision of the Philharmonic agreement (1973).
    This subseries also documents the longstanding negotiations with the City Center of Music and Drama, Inc., leading to its constituency in 1965. Minutes of the meetings of the Lincoln Center Council (1957-1962, 1968-1971) are contained here as well.
    - The Chamber Music Society, 1967 (Box 16, Folder 179)
    - The Chamber Music Society, 1968-1970 (Box 16, Folder 180)
    - The City Center of Music and Drama, Inc. - General Files, 1963-1972 (Box 16, Folder 181)
    - The City Center of Music and Drama, Inc. - Negotiations, n.d., 1955-May 1959 (1977) (Box 16, Folder 182)
    - The City Center of Music and Drama, Inc. - Negotiations, June 1959-1960 (Box 16, Folder 183)
    - The City Center of Music and Drama, Inc. - Negotiations, January-May 1961 (Box 16, Folder 184)
    - The City Center of Music and Drama, Inc. - Negotiations, June 1961-January 28, 1963 (Box 17, Folder 185)
    - The City Center of Music and Drama, Inc. - Negotiations, January 29-December 1963 (Box 17, Folder 186)
    - The City Center of Music and Drama, Inc. - Negotiations, May-July 1964 (Box 17, Folder 187)
    - The City Center of Music and Drama, Inc. - Negotiations, August-October 6, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 188)
    - The City Center of Music and Drama, Inc. - Negotiations, October 11-30, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 189)
    - The City Center of Music and Drama, Inc. - Negotiations, November-December 1964 (Box 17, Folder 190)
    - The City Center of Music and Drama, Inc. - Negotiations, January-November 16, 1965 (Box 17, Folder 191)
    - The City Center of Music and Drama, Inc. - Negotiations, November 22, 1964-1968 (Box 17, Folder 192)
    - Film Society of Lincoln Center, Inc. - Film Festivals, 1962-1965 (Box 17, Folder 193)
    - Film Society of Lincoln Center, Inc. - Film Festivals, 1967-September 1968 (Box 17, Folder 194)
    - Film Society of Lincoln Center, Inc. - Film Festivals, 1969-1972 (Box 17, Folder 195)
    - Film Society of Lincoln Center, Inc. - General Files, n.d., 1962-1964 (Box 17, Folder 196)
    - Film Society of Lincoln Center, Inc. - General Files, 1965-1967 (Box 17, Folder 197)
    - Film Society of Lincoln Center, Inc. - General Files, 1968-1971 (Box 17, Folder 198)
    - The Juilliard School - Dance Division, 1956-1963 (Box 18, Folder 199)
    - The Juilliard School - Dance Division, 1964-1971 (Box 18, Folder 200)
    - The Juilliard School - Drama Training - General Files, 1957-1962 (1972) (Box 18, Folder 201)
    - The Juilliard School - Drama Training - General Files, 1963-1967 (1972) (Box 18, Folder 202)
    - The Juilliard School - Drama Training - General Files, January-February 1968 (1972) (Box 18, Folder 203)
    - The Juilliard School - Drama Training - General Files, March-April 3, 1968 (1972) (Box 18, Folder 204)
    - The Juilliard School - Drama Training - General Files, April 8-December 1968 (1972) (Box 18, Folder 205)
    - The Juilliard School - Drama Training - General Files, 1969-1973 (1972) (Box 18, Folder 206)
    - The Juilliard School - Drama Training - Report - Lincoln Center Juilliard Drama Situation - Review of Carnegie Grants and Lincoln Center Commitments, April 5, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 207)
    - The Juilliard School - General Files, 1955-1972 (1972) (Box 18, Folder 208)
    - The Juilliard School - General Files, 1957-1971 (Box 18, Folder 209)
    - The Juilliard School - "Juilliard School of Music: Preliminary Study of Future Financial Support, April 14, 1961" by Booz, Allen & Hamilton, April-June 1961 (Box 18, Folder 210)
    - The Juilliard School - Juilliard School Use of Alice Tully Hall, 1959-1963 (Box 19, Folder 211)
    - The Juilliard School - Juilliard School Use of Alice Tully Hall, 1964-1972 (Box 19, Folder 212)
    - The Juilliard School - Special Educational Projects, 1959-1963 (1971) (Box 19, Folder 213)
    - Library/Museum of the Performing Arts - General Files, 1956-December 12, 1957 (1971) (Box 19, Folder 214)
    - Library/Museum of the Performing Arts - General Files, December 17, 1957-June 1959 (1971) (Box 19, Folder 215)
    - Library/Museum of the Performing Arts - General Files, July 1959-July 1960 (1971) (Box 19, Folder 216)
    - Library/Museum of the Performing Arts - General Files, 1961-1962 (1971) (Box 19, Folder 217)
      See also RAC Photograph Collection, Series 1073, Box 1, Folder 4.
    - Library/Museum of the Performing Arts - General Files, 1963-1966 (1971) (Box 19, Folder 218)
    - Library/Museum of the Performing Arts - General Files, 1967-1971 (1971) (Box 19, Folder 219)
    - Library/Museum of the Performing Arts - "Report of the Lincoln Center Committee of the New York Public Library, June 10, 1959", 1959-1964 (1971) (Box 19, Folder 220)
    - Lincoln Center Council - General Files, 1957-1965 (Box 19, Folder 221)
    - Lincoln Center Council - Meetings Minutes, 1957-1962 (Box 19, Folder 222)
    - Lincoln Center Council - Meetings Minutes, 1966-March 1968 (Box 19, Folder 223)
    - Lincoln Center Council - Meetings Minutes, April-December 1968 (Box 19, Folder 224)
    - Lincoln Center Council - Meetings Minutes, 1969-1971 (Box 20, Folder 225)
    - Metropolitan Opera Association - Agreement, March-November 1960 (Box 20, Folder 226)
    - Metropolitan Opera Association - Agreement, December 1960-January 1961 (Box 20, Folder 227)
    - Metropolitan Opera Association - Agreement, February-April 10, 1961 (Box 20, Folder 228)
    - Metropolitan Opera Association - Agreement, April 28-May 1961, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 229)
    - Metropolitan Opera Association, Inc. - Annual Reports, 1966-1969 (Box 20, Folder 230)
    - Metropolitan Opera Association, Inc. - General Files, n.d., 1961-1967 (Box 20, Folder 231)
    - Miscellany, 1978 (Box 20, Folder 232)
    - Music Theater of Lincoln Center, 1962-1967 (1971) (Box 20, Folder 233)
    - Negotiations with Major Constituents (Reviewed by S.B. in 1971), 1956-April 1957 (Box 20, Folder 234)
    - Negotiations with Major Constituents (Reviewed by S.B. in 1971), July 1957-May 1959 (Box 20, Folder 235)
    - Negotiations with Major Constituents (Reviewed by S.B. in 1971), June 1959-April 1960 (Box 20, Folder 236)
    - Negotiations with Major Constituents (Reviewed by S.B. in 1971), June 1960-1961 (Box 20, Folder 237)
    - New York Shakespeare Festival - Negotiations with Joseph Papp, 1973 (Box 21, Folder 238)
    - New York State Theater - New York City Ballet Two-Year Residence, 1962-February 1964 (Box 21, Folder 239)
    - New York State Theater - New York City Ballet Two-Year Residence, April-June 1964 (Box 21, Folder 240)
    - New York State Theater - New York City Ballet Two-Year Residence, August 1964-June 1965 (Box 21, Folder 241)
    - Philharmonic-Symphony Society of New York, Inc. - Agreement, 1956-October 17, 1960 (1971) (Box 21, Folder 242)
    - Philharmonic-Symphony Society of New York, Inc. - Agreement, October 24, 1960-April 14, 1961 (1971) (Box 21, Folder 243)
    - Philharmonic-Symphony Society of New York, Inc. - Agreement, April 16-May 15, 1961 (1971) (Box 21, Folder 244)
    - Philharmonic-Symphony Society of New York, Inc. - Agreement, May 19-June 6, 1961 (1971) (Box 21, Folder 245)
    - Philharmonic-Symphony Society of New York, Inc. - Agreement, June 7-14, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 246)
    - Philharmonic-Symphony Society of New York, Inc. - Agreement, June 15, 1961-1965 (1971) (Box 21, Folder 247)
    - Philharmonic-Symphony Society of New York, Inc. - Agreement, 1966-1971 (1971) (Box 21, Folder 248)
    - Philharmonic-Symphony Society of New York, Inc. - General Files, 1958-1963 (1971) (Box 21, Folder 249)
    - Philharmonic-Symphony Society of New York, Inc. - Promenade Concerts, 1962-1965 (1971) (Box 21, Folder 250)
    - Relations Between Lincoln Center, Inc. and Constituents, 1961 (Box 22, Folder 251)
    - Repertory Theater - Brochures, Playbills, n.d., 1963-1966 (Box 22, Folder 252)
    - Repertory Theater - Company Clippings and Correspondence, n.d., 1963-March 1964 (Box 22, Folder 253)
    - Repertory Theater - Company Clippings and Correspondence, April 1964-February 1965 (Box 22, Folder 254)
    - Repertory Theater - Company Clippings and Correspondence, March-December 1965 (Box 22, Folder 255)
    - Repertory Theater - Company Clippings and Correspondence, 1966-1976 (Box 22, Folder 256)
    - Repertory Theater of Lincoln Center - General Files, 1956-1959 (1971) (Box 22, Folder 257)
    - Repertory Theater of Lincoln Center - General Files, 1960-1961 (1971) (Box 22, Folder 258)
    - Repertory Theater of Lincoln Center - General Files, 1962-1963 (1971) (Box 22, Folder 259)
    - Repertory Theater of Lincoln Center - General Files, 1964-1965 (1971) (Box 22, Folder 260)
    - Repertory Theater of Lincoln Center - General Files, 1966-May 1968 (1971) (Box 22, Folder 261)
    - Repertory Theater of Lincoln Center - General Files, 1968-September 1969 (1971) (Box 22, Folder 262)
    - Repertory Theater of Lincoln Center - General Files, October 1969-1970 (1971) (Box 22, Folder 263)
    - Repertory Theater of Lincoln Center - General Files, January-April 11, 1971 (Box 23, Folder 264)
    - Repertory Theater of Lincoln Center - General Files, April 12-May 3, 1971 (Box 23, Folder 265)
    - Repertory Theater of Lincoln Center - General Files, May 4-September 12, 1971 (Box 23, Folder 266)
    - Repertory Theater of Lincoln Center - General Files, September 14-December 3, 1971 (Box 23, Folder 267)
    - Repertory Theater of Lincoln Center - General Files, February-July 1972 (Box 23, Folder 268)
    - Repertory Theater of Lincoln Center - General Files, October-December 1972 (Box 23, Folder 269)
    - Repertory Theater of Lincoln Center - Press Releases, n.d., 1965-1966 (Box 23, Folder 270)
    - Repertory Theater of Lincoln Center - Reports, 1970, 1971 (Box 23, Folder 271)
    - Special Subcommittee re: Effect of Philharmonic Musicians Strike - Revision of Philharmonic Agreement, 1973 (Box 23, Folder 272)
    - Special Subcommittee re: Effect of Philharmonic Musicians Strike - Revision of Philharmonic Agreement, 1974 (Box 23, Folder 273)
    - Special Subcommittee re: Effect of Philharmonic Musicians Strike - Revision of Philharmonic Agreement, 1975 (Box 24, Folder 274)
    - Standards for Constituents, 1957 (Box 24, Folder 275)
  - Education, 1958-1978; 5
    This subseries documents Lincoln Center's commitment to education including the correspondence and reports of the Lincoln Center Committee on Education (1968-1976) and the establishment and expansion of the Lincoln Center Student Program (1960-1972).
    - Cable Television, 1971-1972 (1972) (Box 24, Folder 276)
    - Choral Festival, 1965-March 1969 (Box 24, Folder 277)
    - Choral Festival, May 1969-1972 (Box 24, Folder 278)
      See also RAC Photograph Collection, Series 1073, Box 1, Folder 5.
    - Educational Television, 1958-1967 (Box 24, Folder 279)
    - Fund for Education and Creative Artistic Advancement - General Files, 1960-April 1961 (Box 24, Folder 280)
    - Fund for Education and Creative Artistic Advancement - General Files, May-July 1961 (Box 24, Folder 281)
    - Fund for Education and Creative Artistic Advancement - General Files, 1962-July 1963 (Box 24, Folder 282)
    - Fund for Education and Creative Artistic Advancement - Dr. Max Kaplan, Consultant, 1960-August 1963 (Box 24, Folder 283)
    - Lincoln Center Committee on Education - Carnegie Study - General Files, 1968-1971 (Box 24, Folder 284)
    - Lincoln Center Committee on Education - Carnegie Study - General Files, 1972-1973 (Box 24, Folder 285)
    - Lincoln Center Committee on Education - Carnegie Study - "The Role of the Performing Arts in Four New York Communities" Report, pp. 1-33, June 1971 (Box 25, Folder 286)
    - Lincoln Center Committee on Education - Carnegie Study - "The Role of the Performing Arts in Four New York Communities" Report, pp. 34-54, June 1971 (Box 25, Folder 287)
    - Lincoln Center Committee on Education - Carnegie Study - "The Role of the Performing Arts in Four New York Communities" Report, pp. 55-80, June 1971 (Box 25, Folder 288)
    - Lincoln Center Committee on Education - Carnegie Study - "The Role of the Performing Arts in Four New York Communities" Report, pp. 81-end, June 1971 (Box 25, Folder 289)
    - Lincoln Center Committee on Education - General Files, 1970 (Box 25, Folder 290)
    - Lincoln Center Committee on Education - General Files, January-June 1971 (Box 25, Folder 291)
    - Lincoln Center Committee on Education - General Files, September 1971-February 1972 (Box 25, Folder 292)
    - Lincoln Center Committee on Education - General Files, April-September 1972 (Box 25, Folder 293)
    - Lincoln Center Committee on Education - General Files, October 1972-April 1973 (Box 25, Folder 294)
    - Lincoln Center Committee on Education - General Files, May-December 1973 (Box 25, Folder 295)
    - Lincoln Center Committee on Education - General Files, January-March 1974 (Box 25, Folder 296)
    - Lincoln Center Committee on Education - General Files, April 1974-1976 (Box 25, Folder 297)
    - Lincoln Center Institute, 1978 (Box 26, Folder 298)
    - Student Program - Council on Educational Programs, 1961-1967 (Box 26, Folder 299)
    - Student Program - Council on Educational Programs, 1969-1973 (Box 26, Folder 300)
    - Student Program - General Files, 1960-March 1961 (Box 26, Folder 301)
    - Student Program - General Files, May 1961-1962 (Box 26, Folder 302)
    - Student Program - General Files, 1964-1967 (Box 26, Folder 303)
    - Student Program - "The Hunting of the Squiggle: A Study of a Performing Arts Institution and Young People" by Marc Schubart, 1970-1971 (Box 26, Folder 304)
    - Student Program - "A Teacher's Guide to Lincoln Center" - Booklet, 1971-1972 (Box 26, Folder 305)
    - Student Program - Teacher's Guide - General Files, 1964-1967 (Box 26, Folder 306)
  - Financial Administration, 1956-1972; 6
    This subseries focuses on the financial aspects of the project, including financial policy and planning, budget and construction costs, budget analysis, the capital fund and projected capital needs. Investigators of administrative issues should also consult Subseries 1 - Administration.
    - Auditors' Letters and Management Controls, 1968 (Box 26, Folder 307)
    - Budgetary and Construction Costs Problems, 1958-June 16, 1959 (Box 26, Folder 308)
    - Budgetary and Construction Costs Problems, 1959 June 19-25 (Box 26, Folder 309)
    - Capital Fund - Budgets, 1968-May 1969 (Box 27, Folder 310)
    - Capital Fund - Budgets, June-November 1969 (Box 27, Folder 311)
    - Capital Fund - Budgets, December 1969-February 1970 (Box 27, Folder 312)
    - Capital Fund - Budgets, March 1970 (Box 27, Folder 313)
    - Capital Fund - General Files, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 314)
    - Capital Fund - General Files, 1968 (Box 27, Folder 315)
    - Capital Fund - General Files, 1969-1970 (Box 27, Folder 316)
    - Capital Fund - History, 1966-1970 (Box 27, Folder 317)
    - Capital Fund - Howard Roy Work Papers, 1970 (Box 28, Folder 318)
    - Capital Needs Budget Analyses, etc., 1965-June 1966 (Box 28, Folder 319)
    - Capital Needs Budget Analyses, etc., October 1966-1967 (Box 28, Folder 320)
    - Capital Needs Budget Analyses, etc., 1969-1973 (Box 28, Folder 321)
    - Committee on Financial Policy, Building Committee, 1958-January 1963 (Box 28, Folder 322)
    - Committee on Financial Policy, Building Committee, February-December 1963 (Box 28, Folder 323)
    - Finance Committee (later Investment Committee), 1957-1960 (Box 28, Folder 324)
    - Financial and Policy Problems, January-March 1968 (Box 28, Folder 325)
    - Financial and Policy Problems, April 1-19, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 326)
    - Financial and Policy Problems, 1968 April 22-June 7 (Box 28, Folder 327)
    - Financial and Policy Problems, 1968 June 19-December 31 (Box 28, Folder 328)
    - Financial and Policy Problems, January-May 1969 (Box 29, Folder 329)
    - Financial and Policy Problems, June 1969-December 1970 (Box 29, Folder 330)
    - Financial Policy Memoranda, January 1959-April 1960 (Box 29, Folder 331)
    - Financial Policy Memoranda, May 1960-1964 (Box 29, Folder 332)
    - General Files, June 1956-April 1957 (Box 29, Folder 333)
    - General Files, May-December 1957 (Box 29, Folder 334)
    - General Files, January-August 1958 (Box 29, Folder 335)
    - General Files, September 1958-1959 (Box 29, Folder 336)
    - General Files, February-June 1960 (Box 29, Folder 337)
    - General Files, July 1960-May 1961 (Box 29, Folder 338)
    - General Files, June-December 1961 (Box 29, Folder 339)
    - Requirements for Completion, 1962 (Box 30, Folder 340)
    - Requirements for Completion, 1963-1964 (Box 30, Folder 341)
    - Reports - Financial and Concept Planning, 1956-1957 (Box 30, Folder 342)